# Prakashbhai Koli

#### Computer Science

Experienced IT Specialist with a good background in designing and developing. 1+ years of industry experience. Excellent problem solving skills and ability to perform well in a team. Seeking to help company, as well as grow and develop my own skills.

koliprakashbhai555@gmail.com

Pune, India

prakashbhai555.github.io/pkportfolio/

+91-79723-94788

iii 05 May, 1995

in linkedin.com/in/prakashbhai-koli-99711819b

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## jr. Software Developer (Intern)

## Hands in Technology

01/2020 - 07/2020 Kandivali, Mumbai handsintechnology.com

T - - 1 -

 As Intern was working on Magento2 PHP Framework for updating, solve some config. file bugs, as well as manually Testing some Live Projects on Android, iOS, and web App.

## **Associate Software Engineer**

Vistaar Digital Media Pvt. Ltd.

07/2021 - 03/2022 Boriwali, Mumbai www.vistaardigital.com

 As Software Engineer experienced on developing web application and work on Emailers, Edetailing, Git, SQL, JS, Drupal, WordPress, WIX

### **EDUCATION**

## **Master of Computer Application**

R.C Patel Institute Of Management Research And Development, Shirpur

08/2017 - 04/2020 NMU, Jalgaon

64.00 %

Computer Science

## **Bachelor of Computer Science**

S.P.D.M College, Shirpur

07/2014 - 01/2017 NMU, Jalgaon

62.00 %

- Computer Science

### HSC

#### New High School, Taloda

07/2011 - 05/2012 Nashik Board

51.33

- Science Stream

#### SSC

#### K.P.Patil School, Bhaler

07/2009 - 05/2010 Nashik Board

74.60

Marathi Medium

### **SKILLS**

Team Work

Aultitasking

Helpfu

Energetic

#### **TECHNICAL SKILL**

SQL, PL/SQL, C++

HTML, CSS, PHP

Emailers, Edetailing, Git

Magento2, WordPress, WIX, Figma

#### **COLLEGE PROJECTS**

One Stop NRI Advisory. (Smart Mobile Application)

 In the project Admin can provide the packages and subservices for user to order as per there requirements. The need of this project is Windows platform, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, PHP, MySQL, JS, etc.

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Introduction to WordPress 🗗

Front end Development - HTML

## MY WORK/OTHERS LINKS

Dribbble (UI/UX Designing Portfolio)

Online Shopping (Made with Google Site for shopping)

#### **LANGUAGES**

English Hindi

Professional Working Proficiency Full Professional Proficiency

Marathi

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

## **INTERESTS/HOBBIES**

Puzzle Solving

Photography

Travelling